Hello friends, welcome to my
channel. Today we will learn about the grey market premium and the
company which is going to go down now.
Along with this, its IPO is going to come today, we will
also learn about that, but
before that, like this video of mine
and one thing is that in this IPO, whether it has been
kept for retail quota for 35 years or not,
after that let us know about 4 interests. The
opening date was on 30th,
its closing date is
going to be on 2nd. It is a big IPO, it is of 7250 crores
and apart from that,
its face value is of 2000 crores, I will write it for 900 crores. Its
price band has been kept at
14400, but it is true that for 1 lot
and for Tera Road,
₹187200 for 13 years, you will not get it. It is a
very old company of Anand Rathi ji
and it is opening from 2nd, from tomorrow,
6th is its last date and
set the date on 6th, this is the IPO, it is of
Adani Wilmar's company.  There's a company that's
going to launch an IPO, so that's
pretty amazing
[music]